And once you hit the enter, the AI
is going to think through the course that
you've uploaded.
The video is going to look for each
of the lessons and make sure that they
rhyme.
So when the AI is done working, what
we are expecting to see at the end
of the day is that in this, each
of our lessons, we want to see the
respective video that tally with the lesson, you
know, so rather than coming here to upload
it one by one on the likes, you
can just also give that task to AI
to handle for you.
Okay.
Let's go see.
Our AI is working.
The AI is done linking every of them,
even though it's giving me updates about, um,
completion.
Yeah.
So transcoding or the validation of the video
is telling me that some are pending while
some are not.
And of course the AI is right.
Because if you come here, you see that
you have two pending, the rest are completed.